adlabsimagica.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist on the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any modification and changes, please review this policy periodically. By accessing this website, www.adlabsimagica.com you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this website please do not use or access our website. By accessing this website, certain information about you, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigation through the website, the systems and programs used and the time spent, along with other similar information, may be stored on our servers. We want you to feel confident about using www.adlabsimagica.com to plan and purchase your tickets, so we are committed to protecting the information we gather from you. While no website can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data ccuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current internet security methods and technologies. By mere use of the website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use. 

### 1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and Other Information

When you use our website, we collect and store your personal information from you. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our website to make your experience safer and easier. Importantly, we only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. In general, you can browse the website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Wherever possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the website. You may provide us with a user ID. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include but not limited to the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our website or not), your computer browser information, your IP address etc. We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the website to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser on your system. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookies". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. If you choose to buy on the website, we collect information about your buying behaviour. If you transact with us, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details and tracking information from cheques or money orders. If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. 

### 2\. Use of Demographics / Profile Data / Your data

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we may provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection of information. In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in--and to display content according to your preferences. 

### 3.Sharing of Information

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public. We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

### 4.Links to Other Sites

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. www.adlabsimagica.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked or hypertext linked websites. 

### 5.Security Precautions

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

### 6.Choice/Opt Out

We may or may not allow all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. 

### 7.Advertising on www.adlabsimagica.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

### 8.Your Consent

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to “Your consent” for sharing your information as per this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

### 9.Minors

As we cannot distinguish the age of persons who access our Website, a blanket privacy policy is applied. www.adlabsimagica.com does not seek or intend to seek to receive any personal information from minors (i.e. eighteen years of age as per Indian legislations). Should a parent or guardian have reason to believe that a minor has provided www.adlabsimagica.com with personal information without their prior consent, please contact us to ensure that the personal information is removed and unsubscribe them from any promotional contact opportunities. 

### 10.Security

[www.adlabsimagica.com](http://www.adlabsimagica.com/) has implemented technology and security features to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. A secure server protects your personal information. Additionally you can be assured that the information you provide to www.adlabsimagica.com is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. If you become aware of any security breach, please let us know as soon as possible. We have internal procedures in place requiring our employees and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by www.adlabsimagica.com [www.adlabsimagica.com](http://www.adlabsimagica.com/) will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information which we hold about you. Your personal information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. Unfortunately, despite the aforementioned technology and security features, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot give an absolute assurance that the personal information you provide to us will be secure at all times, and we cannot be responsible for any event arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. www.adlabsimagica.com will not be held responsible for events arising from third parties gaining unauthorized access to your personal information Please note also that www.adlabsimagica.com may use overseas facilities to process or back up your personal information. As a result, we may transfer to and store your personal information at our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to safeguard your privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### 11.Contact Us

If you have any queries regarding our Privacy Policy, or should you have reason to believe that a breach of privacy has occurred, please submit your concerns to [contactus@adlabsimagica.com](mailto:contactus@adlabsimagica.com) or in writing to the following address Guests are informed that they may be photographed/videographed during their visit to Adlabs Imagica and such photographs/video recordings may be used by Adlabs Imagica for promotional purposes.
